businesscard2.com 2010-11-20

# Privacy Policy | BusinessCard2

* * *

### Our Commitment to Privacy

We are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our pledge is to secure certain information that you provide us, and to make every reasonable effort to use this information only as you choose. We are pleased to take a leadership role in assisting our customers and other businesses in understanding the importance of using your personal information appropriately.

### Cookies and Personal Information

Cookies (small bits of information that websites send to your computer) are used in our system to allow users to login faster. You can turn off this feature in your browser, but be aware that disabling your cookies may adversely affect performance on BusinessCard2.com and could even cause some site features to work incorrectly. 

When you visit BusinessCard2.com we collect data from your computer. This data can include your IP address, browser type, the pages you view on BusinessCard2, referring URL and date/time information. The primary use of this information is to deliver you an optimal experience on our site, and help guide future website development.

Shared objects (sometimes referred to as Flash cookies) may be used in identifying your computer and associating you to where your BusinessCard2 resides on the internet. In addition, when you digitally “pass” your BusinessCard2 we may use such shared objects to recognize you, although we do so with unique tokens. You can modify the Settings Manager here: <http://macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>. 

We collect personal information online when:

  * you register with us
  * you register to receive emails
  * you conduct online transactions
  * you submit questions or comments to us
  * you submit questions or information to other users
  * you request information or materials
  * you participate in online communications
  * you request we send information
  * you are logged in and view other business cards

We use the personal information you provide to:

  * Register you in the registration and email programs, create and maintain accounts process, fulfill, and follow up on site processes, answer your e-mail and send information.
  * Provide you with information related to your account, the products or services you use, to better understand your needs and interests, to improve our service and to personalize communications.
  * Deliver the BusinessCard2 web container. In most cases, this includes the information you have chosen to display, including, but not limited to, first and last name, company, job title, phone number, fax number, email address, street/city/state/postal address, biographical data, and other information necessary in making it easy for potential customers to both understand and reach out to you.

### Sharing Your Information

BusinessCard2 has been designed to maintain and distribute your professional identity.   
BusinessCard2 has been designed to for commercial purposes only. We advise against using it to store personal information. Nevertheless, we will not sell, rent, or trade the information you provide online unless you permit us to do so. We do share your information with certain business clients and partners as part of the product or service offering of the company and your participation therein. We may disclose information to third parties without your consent for any of the following reasons: to comply with any law, regulation or court order, to cooperate with Government investigations, to help prevent fraud or to enforce or protect the rights of businesscard2.com, a service of Workface Inc., its divisions, or its subsidiaries. We reserve the right to transfer your information in connection with the sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets. If the business is sold or transferred, we may give you an opportunity to tell us not to transfer your information. In some cases, this may mean that the new organization will not be able to continue providing you the services or products that Workface provided.

### Contact Importer

The BusinessCard2 contact importer tool allows you to upload your contacts for the purpose of inviting and connecting with the professionals in your network online, as well as sharing your BusinessCard2 with your contacts. This helps establish credibility and a community around your profile. If you enter in your password for other contact management programs you use to access your contacts, your password is not stored in our system, nor does anyone have access to view it. 

When you use the invite system in BusinessCard2, we will send invites on your behalf using your name. We may send follow up emails as well, but there will always be opt out options for these contacts if they no longer wish to receive these messages. The contact information provided will be stored indefinitely to help ensure that users that opt out of messages will never receive messages, and also if any contacts who join BusinessCard2 can be easily connected with users in their network. 

### Your Choices About Receiving Email

We may send you e-mail as part of the private messaging system, with details about your account, or in response to your questions. Businesscard2.com, a part of Workface Inc., its divisions, and its subsidiaries may also send you e-mail with information about products and services that may be of interest to you. We will give you an opportunity to let us know your preference when you register for a service, when you provide us with your personal information, or when we send you e-mail. This option applies to promotional e-mail only, as we may find it necessary to send you e-mail relating to your account or order, or as part of the services that you have subscribed to.

### Changes to this Privacy Notice

We reserve the right to modify this privacy notice from time to time, by posting a prominent announcement on this page, by changing the date of modification or, in the event of a material change, by notifying by e-mail all customers whose personal information we have retained. 

This Privacy Notice was last amended on 04/25/2010.
